{
    "subject": "resource/Kiss_Me_Good-Bye",
    "predicate": "ontology/subsequentWork",
    "object": "resource/This_Love_(Angela_Aki_song)",
    "human_readable": "Kiss Me Good-Bye is followed by This Love (Angela Aki song).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.981744110584259,
            "question": "What song follows 'Kiss Me Good-Bye' by Angela Aki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9432336688041687,
            "question": "Which Angela Aki song comes after 'Kiss Me Good-Bye'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8245697021484375,
            "question": "What is the title of the song that follows 'Kiss Me Good-Bye'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8194549679756165,
            "question": "Is 'This Love' an Angela Aki song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8100119233131409,
            "question": "According to this statement, what song order follows 'Kiss Me Good-Bye'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5850361585617065,
            "question": "What is the relationship between 'Kiss Me Good-Bye' and 'This Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40278181433677673,
            "question": "Can you list Angela Aki songs in the order mentioned?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38017889857292175,
            "question": "What musical work is associated with the phrase 'Kiss Me Good-Bye'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3126654028892517,
            "question": "Who is the artist of the song 'This Love'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16598185896873474,
            "question": "Name the two songs mentioned in this statement."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kiss Me Good-Bye is followed by This Love (Angela Aki song).",
            "html": "dbpedia_1898_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the artist of the song 'This Love'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1898_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical work is associated with the phrase 'Kiss Me Good-Bye'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1898_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you list Angela Aki songs in the order mentioned?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1898_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1898_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1898_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1898_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1898_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1898_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1898_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1898_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1898_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1898_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1898_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided documents discuss the song \"Kiss Me Good-bye\" by Angela Aki and do not mention any information about a song titled \"This Love\" by Angela Aki.  Therefore, we cannot confirm if \"Kiss Me Good-Bye\" is followed by \"This Love\". \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about the song \"Kiss Me Good-Bye\" being followed by another song titled \"This Love.\" All the documents are related to the song \"Kiss Me Good-Bye,\" its lyrics, and its significance but do not mention any subsequent song."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "'Kiss Me Good-Bye' is not followed by 'This Love', according to the provided context, as there is no information suggesting another song named 'This Love' by Angela Aki.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text focuses on the song \"Kiss Me Good-Bye\" by Angela Aki, offering information about its release, meaning, and context within Final Fantasy XII. There is no mention of another Angela Aki song titled \"This Love.\"",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The provided context does not mention any song titled \"This Love\" by Angela Aki following \"Kiss Me Good-Bye.\" The information given focuses on the song \"Kiss Me Good-Bye\" and its details, without referencing another song called \"This Love.\"",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}